https://www.alexandertechnologies.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Statement
Alexander Battery Technologies welcomes your interest in this website (www.alexandertechnologies.com). The Alexander Battery Technologies address responsible for it is:
Alexander Technologies Europe Ltd 4 Doxford Drive; South West Industrial Park Peterlee, Co Durham, UK SR8 2RL
We take your privacy seriously and want you to understand our practices with respect to the handling of your personal data. This privacy statement explains how we do this.
When we collect your personal data
If you decide to contact us or make use of personalized services (e.g. by contact us form, more information form, or RFQ form), then you will be asked to submit the limited personal data which is necessary for us to provide that service or handle your query. This is completely voluntary.
If you ask us to send you information, brochures, or battery quotes, we rely on your active consent in order to do so. You may opt out of receiving these communications at any time.
If any form which collects your personal data allows you to voluntarily provide additional information, we seek this information because we think it will help us to give you a better-quality service. You do not have to provide such information if you do not wish to do so.
We also collect personal data from ‘cookies’.
Site traffic information and cookies
To learn about what cookies and similar technologies are, we recommend that you visit the following third-party website: http://www.allaboutcookies.org/.
Like many websites, we use cookies for a variety of purposes. These technologies collect information about your device hardware and interactions with our site.
This information helps us to continuously improve our site's content and functionality by analyzing where, on which types of devices and how our site is used, how many visitors we receive, and where they click through to the site from; and remember you in case you re-visit our site, so we will know if you have already been served with cookie banners, surveys, or (where site content is undergoing testing) which version of the content you were served.
To delete or stop cookies being placed on your computer, please check the help menu of your internet browser. Blocking cookies will reduce the functionality of this website.
Who do we share your personal data with and where does it go?
We may store or transfer your personal data to our other Alexander Battery Technologies locations around the world. We do this under our group-wide binding corporate rules, which guarantee an adequate level of data protection wherever your data is physically kept.
We also use the services of third-party service providers to host our website. Any third-party provider we appoint must act in accordance with our written instructions when processing your personal data and must protect your personal data in line with the contractually required security measures. Where we store or transfer your personal data to a third-party provider based outside the UK and European Economic Area, we take steps to ensure your personal data is adequately protected.
We have the right to disclose your personal data as required by law, or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, request from a regulator or any other legal process served on Alexander Battery Technologies. If there is a takeover, sale or purchase of our business, we may disclose your personal data to the new (or prospective) owner of the business.
How long do we keep your information?
We will only hold your information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it was collected, before making it non-identifiable or deleting it.
If you send us any ‘contact us’ messages, we will delete or de-identify these messages once we have finally satisfied your query.
If you choose to unsubscribe from a service, we may keep a ‘suppression list’ containing your details so we know you have unsubscribed.
Your rights, complaints and how to contact us
You have the right to access your personal data and ask for it to be rectified or deleted at any later time.
If you have questions or concerns relating to the handling of your personal data, or other privacy related query, please get in touch by clicking here.
Our website may contain links to third-party sites. This privacy statement does not apply to those third-party sites.
Alexander Technologies Announces it is now DBA as Alexander Battery Technologies
Experts in Battery Design and Manufacturing Highlighting ISO 13485 and ISO 9001 Quality Systems
USA Location
Alexander Technologies Europe Limited
1580 15th Street S.W.
Alexander Battery Technologies continues the fight against COVID-19
Alexander Battery Technologies Completes Factory Expansion
Alexander Technologies Announces it is now DBA as Alexander Battery Technologies
